have a new analogy for game a and game B
game a is a Island we can all
acknowledge is sinking
it only has so many resources on it and
we're overusing them but and we know
there's often the distant lands a game B
of abundance anti rivalry so Omni way
what would be the best way to find game
B it would not be for all of us to get
on one giant cruise ship fight over who
has control of the steering who thinks
it's in what direction and unanimously
go towards it instead what we would want
is many vessels going out and when
somebody does find it they can call in
the rest and so that is what we are
doing in game B is finding the mini
vessels that are ours to steer and going
off in that direction and when we find
it we will call in the rest and as we go
we are calling in the rest but coming
into game B and wondering where this
giant ship is and arguing about which
way to steer it
isn't getting us there any faster find
your vessel either jump on board someone
that's already there and offer to help
crew it or start your own vessel and ask
for other people to come help crew it
thank you